So, one of my favorite
video games of all time
(Leonard:)is called Shadow
of the Colossus,
and it was only
(Leonard:)for PlayStation 2,
(Leonard:)but then they came out
with a new version
(Leonard:)for PS3 with better graphics.
(Leonard:)I finally got the chance
to play it,
(Leonard:)and for some reason, it just
wasn't as good as the first one.
(Leonard:)Or something about yoga.
(Penny:)I'm sorry--
I was thinking about work.
(Leonard:)Well, I was just saying that
there was this video game...
(Penny:)Yeah, that's when I started
thinking about work.
(Penny:)Uh, listen, I've got
some good news.
(Leonard:)Hmm.
(Penny:)This is for you.
(Leonard:)Huh.
(Leonard:)What is this?
(Penny:)Well, you know how
they gave me the company car?
(Penny:)Didn't make sense to have two,
so I sold the other one.
(Leonard:)The one I gave you?
(Penny:)Yeah. And there's your money
back-- and now we're even.
(laughs):
How great is that?
(Leonard:)Uh, yeah.
(Penny:)What?